-大伙们  票已经开卖啦  -什么
- Guys, tickets already went on sale! - What?!
不应该现在就开卖啊
They're not supposed to be available yet.
我也不知道原因  但就是开卖了
I don't know what to tell you, but they're on sale!
等等  你确定是新的《星球大战》电影票吗
What? Wait. You're sure they're Star Wars tickets?
不  是《钢木兰2:  钢上加钢》的票
No, it's Steel Magnolias 2: Even Steelier.
网页卡住了  我上不了
The Web site's frozen. I can't get in!
我也是
Same here!
-这样下去票会卖光的  -我们该怎么办
- Guys, they're gonna sell out! - What are we gonna do?!
好吧  虽然这违背我一直以来的信仰
All right, this goes against everything I stand for,
但走投无路  也只能出此下策
but desperate times call for desperate measures.
主啊
Lord...
我是谢尔顿·库珀
This is Sheldon Cooper.
您跟我母亲是好朋友
You're good friends with my mom.
我知道我这辈子一直在否认您的存在
I know I've spent my life denying that you exist.
-买到了  -我还会继续否认下去
- Got 'em! - And I will continue to do so!
翻译：最重要的大雕赛  最重要的小萌猫
丁小七  猫中之王
你跟艾米和好如初我好高兴
I'm really happy you and Amy are back together.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
我也很高兴  但我假装不了是为你高兴
I'm also really happy, but I can't pretend it's for you.
新星战电影三天后要上啦
New Star Wars in three days!
鉴于周四还不能马上到来
Hey, Thursday can't get here soon enough.
我要请假不上班  在家看原作三部曲
I'm taking off work to watch the original trilogy
还要一边吃[掐死]伍基人星战谷麦片
while I eat enough Star Wars cereal to choke a Wookiee.
亲爱的  你知道周四是艾米的生日吧
Uh, sweetie, you do realize Thursday is Amy's birthday.
那你也知道我买票的时候
And you do realize I bought my ticket
我跟艾米还没有复合呢
when Amy and I were broken up?
希望板子上没有你需要的东西了
I hope you didn't need anything in that case,
因为已经拍板定案了
'cause it's closed.
你们才刚刚复合
You guys just got back together.
她生日那天抛下她不太妙吧
You might not want to ditch her on her birthday.
我觉得佩妮说得有道理  你可以改天看嘛
I think Penny has a point. You can see it another day.
但别人可能会剧透啊
But someone might spoil the movie.
但艾米的生日别人就没办法剧透
No one can spoil Amy's birthday for me.
"惊喜  她又老一岁了"
Surprise! She's even older.
真是"万万没想到"啊
Who saw that coming?
这话真"甜蜜"
Oh, that's nice.
写到她蛋糕上去吧
Put that on her cake.
这下好  又来了
Oh, great. This again.
亚瑟  什么风把你给吹来了
Arthur, what brings you back?
你把我问倒了  我...
Uh, beats me. I-I just...
只希望入的不是春梦
hope this isn't a-a sex dream.
过去你曾在我
In the past, you've come to me
碰到困境的时候来指点迷津
when I'm struggling with a dilemma.
还有一次是在你晚上害怕
And-and the one time where... where you were afraid,
需要我来...  当夜灯
and you needed me for... for a night light.
什么事困扰到你了
What's-what's troubling you?
我的小伙伴们跟我说
My friends are telling me
我不应该在女朋友生日时抛下她
I shouldn't abandon my girlfriend on her birthday
跑去看新的《星球大战》
to see the new Star Wars movie.
感觉说得没错啊
Well, sounds right.
我能脱下这身...
Can... can I get out of this...
夏威夷妇女穆穆袍了吗
muumuu now?
这是绝地武士的袍子
Those are the robes of the Jedi,
是银河系和平与正义的守护者呢
the guardians of peace and justice in the galaxy.
他们...  他们都不穿小内内
And they... they-they don't wear underwear.
所以你也同意他们的话
So, you agree with my friends
我不应该去看首映吗
that I should skip the premiere?
你爱那个女孩吗
Uh, do... do you love this girl?
爱
Yes.
但她知道《星球大战》对我有多重要
But she knows how important Star Wars is to me.
或许你应该证明给她看看
Well, maybe you should show her how...
她在你心中到底多重要
how important she is to you.
其方式是看她希望我看的电影吗
By seeing the movie she'd want me to see?
谢尔顿  你有数不清的时间能看这电影
Sheldon, you-you can see this movie whenever you want.
但你能跟这女孩在一起的时间
But you only have a limited number of days
却是有限的
that you-you can be with this woman.
陪她吧
Be with her.
你说得对
You're right.
太好了
Great.
你要上哪去
Where are you going?
我不知道
I don't know,
但希望是一个我能穿裤子的地方
but hopefully, somewhere I can wear pants.
谢尔顿  怎么了
Sheldon, what's wrong?
我想让你知道我会陪你过生日
I wanted to let you know I'll be spending your birthday with you.
好的
Okay.
本来那晚我有《星球大战》首映会的票
See, I-I had tickets to the Star Wars premiere that night,
可质子教授入我的梦  身上还穿着
but Professor Proton came to me in a dream dressed as
绝地武士欧比旺·肯诺比的衣服来劝我陪你
Obi-Wan Kenobi and convinced me I should be with you.
欧比啥
Obi-what?
不打扰你了  你先回去睡吧  晚安
I'll-I'll let you get back to sleep now. Good night.
好  晚安
Okay. Good night.
等等  谢尔顿
Wait. Um, Sheldon,
本来我生日那天你是不打算陪我的吗
were you actually not gonna spend my birthday with me?
时间晚了  要睡了  再见
It's late. Got to go. Bye.
谢尔顿决定陪艾米过生日  这事得点个赞
Good for Sheldon deciding to stay with Amy on her birthday.
对啊
I know.
去看电影时少了他还是会有点怪
It's still gonna be weird to see the movie without him.
我们可以多等两天  等他一起看啊
Well, we could wait a couple days and see it together.
你们好啊
Hello.
我们要去漫画书店  你要一起吗
We're going to the comic book store. You want to come?
去不了
No, I can't.
我得为艾米的生日做准备
I need to make preparations for Amy's birthday.
因此我要先把这件事干了
Which leads me to the following bit of business.
这是我《星球大战》的电影票
This is my ticket to Star Wars.
不用我说你也知道这张票的价值
I don't have to tell you it is worth far more
远远超过面额上的15.5美元
than its face value of $15.50.
我相信你会把它交给值得拥有的人
I trust you'll give it to someone worthy.
没问题
You got it.
佩妮可能会想跟我们一起去看
Well, Penny might want to join us.
这是我《星球大战》的电影票
This is my ticket to Star Wars.
佩妮
Penny.
Penny?
佩妮
如果是我回"请进"会怎么样
What happens if I say, "Come in"?
试试看呗
Well, find out.
请进
Come in!
伯纳黛特
Bernadette?
伯纳黛特  伯纳黛特
Bernadette? Bernadette?
请进
Come in!
你俩就闹吧
Keep it up.
反正我有的是时间
I got nowhere else to be.
快进来吧
Just come in.
以后如果我想看《贱女孩》这部片
For future reference, if I want to watch Mean Girls,
我会直接去网上看
I'll stream it on Netflix.
抱歉啦  你找我们干嘛
We're sorry. What do you need?
你们也知道
Well, as you know,
我会陪艾米一起庆祝生日
I'll be celebrating Amy's birthday with her,
我需要你们的协助
and I could use your assistance
帮我挑出最完美的礼物
in helping me select the perfect gift.
当然可以
Sure.
目前为止我有三个想法
Well, so far, I've come up with three ideas.
第一个是一个跟洛杉矶爱乐管弦乐团
The first is a chance for her to play the harp
演奏竖琴的机会
with the L.A. Philharmonic.
哇  你真的能安排这事吗
Wow. You can really arrange that?
机会嘛  可能有也可能没有
Well, I said a chance, you know.
你跟连锁餐厅说今天是自己生日
When you tell them it's your birthday at Bennigan's,
他们也会大开方便之门
they make a fuss.
我觉得洛杉矶爱乐管弦乐团也会这样吧
I don't see why the Philharmonic would be any different.
不如来点实际的
How about something a little more realistic?
艾米喜欢自己织毛衣
Well, Amy enjoys knitting her own sweaters,
我在想自掏腰包赞助她去参加
so I was thinking of getting her an all-expense-paid trip
威斯康辛州羊及羊毛节
to the Wisconsin Sheep and Wool Festival.
抱歉  我刚才在等你说"逗你玩"
Sorry. I was waiting for the bazinga.
等等  那也可以很浪漫啊
Hold on. It could be romantic.
他们俩一起远离尘嚣
The two of them away together,
在白雪皑皑的威斯康辛州相互取暖
keeping each other warm in snowy Wisconsin.
不不不  她自己去而已
No, no, no, no. She'd be going alone.
如果你们觉得我很怕鸟
Well, if you think I'm afraid of birds,
那真该看看我遇到羊会怎么样
you should see me around sheep.
好吧  第三个选项是什么
Okay, well, what's the third option?
我跟她交媾
That I have coitus with her.
你们觉得把谢尔顿的票给斯尔图特怎么样
What do you think about giving Sheldon's ticket to Stuart?
不知道
I don't know.
你们跟斯尔图特一起看过电影吗
Have you ever seen a movie with Stuart before?
感觉就像跟自己爷爷去看电影
It's like going with your grandpa.
不吃爆米花
Instead of eating popcorn,
他自带保鲜盒装的鸡肉片
he brings little pieces of chicken in Tupperware
还有保温瓶盛满了热汤
and a thermos full of soup.
他没那么糟啦
He's not that bad.
斯尔图特  你周四晚上有事吗
Hey, Stuart, got any plans Thursday night?
我的医生担心我的血液循环
My, uh... my doctor's worried about my circulation,
所以我本来打算去商场走走
so I was thinking about walking around the mall.
怎么了
Why?
你们好啊
Hey, you guys.
记得穿舒服点的鞋子哦
Oh, make sure to wear sensible shoes.
威尔  周四想一起去看《星球大战》吗
Wil, want to go to Star Wars Thursday?
当然好啊
Absolutely.
好啊  带威尔去吧
Fine, take Wil.
看他会不会给你们带蛤蜊浓汤
See if he brings you clam chowder.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
我们...我们再过一遍所有选项
Let's-let's... let's just recap our options.
有竖琴演奏  绵羊织毛
All right, we've got harp thing, sheep thing...
狂野做爱
Wild thang.
你们觉得她最喜欢哪一个
Which do you think she'd prefer?
因为我查过羊及羊毛节的官网
Because I checked the Sheep and Wool Festival Web site,
只剩8千张票了
and there's only 8,000 tickets left.
谢尔顿  跟艾米发生肉体关系可是重大的一步啊
Sheldon, being physical with Amy is a huge step for you.
是啊  你准备好了吗
Yeah, are you ready for this?
任何形式的亲密对我来说都是挑战
Intimacy in any form has been challenging for me,
但我想向她证明她对我有多重要
but I'd like to show her how important she is,
而我感觉现在就是最好的时机
and it feels like now might be the right time.
谢尔顿  这理由太美了
Sheldon, that's so beautiful.
那就这么定了
Then it's settled.
艾米的生日礼物就是我的生殖器
Amy's birthday present will be my genitals.
多谢你们带我出去
Thanks for taking me out.
既然你的生日要跟谢尔顿一起过
Well, you're spending your birthday with Sheldon.
何不跟我们提前庆祝呢
Why not celebrate early?
你想去哪里
So where do you want to go?
我听说格林路上那间新的墨西哥餐厅不错
I heard that new Mexican place on Green Street is good.
好啊
Sure, sure.
或者我们可以带你去做比基尼蜜蜡脱毛
Or we could take you to get a bikini wax.
为什么我生日要做比基尼蜜蜡脱毛
Why would I get a bikini wax for my birthday?
不知道  我就随口一说
Uh, I don't know. It was just a thought.
我觉得还是去吃墨西哥菜好了
I think I'll just stick to Mexican.
很好  吃完以后我们可以去看部小黄片
Great. And then maybe after, we can watch a dirty movie,
如果有人对怎么回事或怎么做有疑问
and if anybody has any questions about what happened or how,
我们可以负责解答
we can answer them.
好吧  到底怎么回事
Okay, what is going on?
我们只是希望你对
Oh, we just want you to be prepared
明天可能发生的惊喜做好准备
for any surprises that might happen tomorrow.
什么惊喜
What surprises?
我们不想剧透坏了惊喜
We don't want to spoil anything,
但谢尔顿说
but you should know that
他做好跟你发生肉体关系的准备了
Sheldon said he's ready to be physical.
你们少他妈逗我玩
You shut your damn mouth!
你们真的听到他这么说了吗
You actually heard him say this?
是的  他说了他想做点什么
Yes. He said he wants to do something
来证明你对他有多重要
to show you how much you mean to him.
真不敢相信
I-I can't believe it. I...
我不知道该说什么了
I don't know what to say.
我们很为你高兴
Well, we're really happy for you,
我们都知道他多看重...
and we know how much he cares...
我知道说什么了  快给我下体除毛
I do know what to say! Let's get me waxed!
为什么永远都不是安吉·迪金森的卧室
Why isn't it ever Angie Dickinson's bedroom?
你回来了
You're back.
这似乎不是我能决定的
It-it doesn't seem like it's up to me.
我猜你来是因为
I suppose you're here because...
我决定跟我的女朋友发生肉体关系了
I've decided to be physical with my girlfriend,
而我以前从来没有做过
and I've never done that before.
稍等一下
E-Excuse me for a moment.
至少努力过了
Well, it was worth a shot.
所以你能帮我吗
So, can you help me?
好吧
Uh, all right. Um...
当一个男人
once-once the man gets
把一个女人的灯笼内裤脱掉
the-the woman out of her... out of her bloomers...
不  不是那个
Oh, no. Not that.
我知道"做"法
I-I understand the mechanics.
很好  因为...
Oh, good, good. 'Cause, uh,
我完全不知道现在的孩子们
I have no idea what kids these days are...
都怎么称呼他们的"部位"
calling their-their parts.
他们好像是说"大屌"[垃圾]
I think they say "junk".
这世界到底怎么了
What is happening to this world?
你究竟想知道什么
What-what do you actually need to know?
那一晚将对我俩来说都很重要
This is an important night for us,
我有点担心自己会太紧张
and I'm worried I might be overwhelmed
然后搞砸了
and ruin everything.
谢尔顿  如果对方是对的人
Sheldon, if-if you're with the right person,
一切都会水到渠成
it-it'll be okay.
谢谢你  亚瑟
Thank you, Arthur.
你是世界上最有智慧的人
You are the wisest of the wise.
很高兴你能这么说
Well, that's-that's very nice of you to say,
可我觉得我只不过是
but I think I'm just an expression of...
你潜意识的映射
of your unconscious mind.
当然了
Oh, sure. Yeah.
但是看着你挺好玩的嘛
Well, you're fun to look at.
就是今晚了
Tonight's the night!
是啊  终于等到了
Yeah, the wait is finally over!
对啊  你们终于可以不再提这事了
I know. Then you'll finally stop talking about it!
-准备好了吗  -来吧
- Ready to go? - Let's do this.
祝你们开心哦
Have fun, guys!
-我们会的  -不敢相信谢尔顿会放弃这个
- We will. - I can't believe Sheldon gave this up.
是啊  我们肯定会玩得比他开心得多
I know. We're gonna have so much more fun than him.
不  他们不会的
No, they're not.
依他们的尿性  会的
Knowing them, they will.
倒数15分钟
T minus 15 minutes!
威尔联系你了吗
Oh, did you hear from Wil?
他在路上了
Yeah, he's on his way.
膀胱检查时间
Time for bladder check.
检查完毕
Check.
检查完毕  等等
Check. Wait.
管他的  我决定忍着
Screw it. I'm holding it.
大家都在嘘什么
What is everyone booing at?
各位  你们好吗
Hey, guys. What's up?
威尔  你在干什么
Um, hey, Wil. What you doin'?
我演过《星际迷航》  当然要支持自家人
I was on Star Trek. I'm just rooting for the home team.
《星际迷航》烂透了
Star Trek stinks!
是吗  生生不息  滚你妈逼
Yeah? Live long and suck it!
生日女孩
Birthday girl.
生日女孩  生日女孩
Birthday girl. Birthday girl.
快进来
Come in!
你好  谢尔顿
Hi, Sheldon.
你好  抱歉我迟到了
Hello. Sorry I'm late.
我本来还给你带了一个气球
I also got you a balloon,
可是它飞走了  我追了好久
but it floated away, and I chased it for a while.
没关系  快进来吧
That's okay. Come on in.
谢谢你
Thank you. Mm-hmm.
我拿个花瓶装上
Um, I'll... I'm gonna go put these in water.
感觉很不一样嘛
Ooh, this is different, hmm?
蜡烛和音乐
Candles and music.
你喜欢吗
Do you like it?
有点吓人
It's kind of spooky.
我可以换回原样
I can change it back.
不不  这是你的生日
No, no, no. It's your birthday.
只要面具杀人魔杰森别突然跳出来就好
As long as no one jumps out in a hockey mask, I'll be fine.
所以...
So...
你今晚想做什么
What'd you have in mind for tonight?
我本来想带你去吃一顿生日大餐
I thought I could take you out to a nice birthday dinner.
如果选个东边的餐厅  说不定还能把气球找回来
If we pick a place east of here, we might find the balloon.
听起来不错  可是...
Um, that sounds nice, but...
我现在不是很饿
I'm not really hungry right now.
我想咱们不如...
I thought maybe...
先"上"礼物吧
we could do presents first.
好呀
All right.
关于这件礼物  我有些事要先告诉你
I should probably tell you something about this gift.
你是说在你...
You mean before you...
"给我"之前吗
give it to me?
是的
Yes.
我可以先问一个问题吗  在我...
May I ask you a question before I...
"给你"之前
give it to you?
-当然  -为什么我们要把
- Of course. - Why are we saying
"给你"说得这么诡异
"give it to you" like that?
谢尔顿
Sheldon,
我知道你的礼物...
I know your present is...
就是今夜与我共享鱼水之欢
for us to be intimate tonight.
我明白了
I see.
你愿意吗
Is that all right?
抱歉  如今这社会动不动就告上法庭
I'm sorry, but this is a litigious society.
我需要你的口头同意
I'm gonna need verbal consent.
求之不得
Yes.
我还是上网下载一个简易合同吧
You know what, let me pull a quick contract off the Internet.
如果你不喜欢《星球大战》  那你干嘛还来呢
So, if you don't like Star Wars, why are you here?
我只是图一乐
Oh, I'm just having fun.
每个人都对这电影这么认真看待
Everyone takes Star Wars so seriously.
就好像电影拍砸了  他们的人生也就毁了
Like if the movie's bad, it's gonna ruin their lives.
电影拍砸了吗  你听说了什么吗
Is it bad? Did you hear something?
亲娘耶  拍砸了  谁赶紧来杀了我吧
Oh, my God. It's bad. Somebody kill me.
看到没  我就是指这种人
See? That's what I mean.
当你明早从晨光中醒来
When you wake up in the morning, whether this is
不管这电影是神作一部  还是狗屎一坨
the greatest movie ever or a total piece of crap,
你的生活都不会有任何改变
your life isn't gonna change at all.
他说得对
He's right.
没错
Yeah.
不管发生什么
No matter what happens,
我们明天都会再来看一遍
we're coming back tomorrow to watch it again.
你觉得谢尔顿真的会跟艾米滚成床单吗
Do you think Sheldon's actually gonna go through with it?
我不知道
I don't know.
他说他已经准备好了
He said he's ready.
没错  可是他还发誓说
Yeah, but he also swore this was the year
今年一定有勇气把南瓜内瓤掏出来呢
he'd be able to pull the guts out of a pumpkin.
我对谢尔顿有信心  我们聊过了
Well, I'm gonna stay positive. I mean, we talked.
我告诉他女生的喜好  他咯咯傻笑了一阵后
I told him what women like, and after he stopped giggling,
看起来相当有自信
he seemed pretty sure of himself.
你好
hi.
Hello.
那个...
So, um...
我该跟你一起钻进被子里吗
should I get under the covers with you?
好呀
All right.
-你好  -你好啊
- Hello. - Hi!
你怎么在发抖  你很冷吗
Why are you shaking? Are you cold?
我只是有点  太紧张
I'm just, um... really nervous.
为什么
Why?
我等待这一刻等得太久了
I've been waiting for this for so long,
我...脑补过太多
I've just... built it up in my head.
我不知道接下来该期待什么
I don't know what to expect.
我也不知道
Neither do I.
但是...我们可以一起找出答案
But... we can find out together.
好的
Okay.
我真的好紧张
I'm really nervous.
我知道
I know.
我们等待这一刻等得太久了
We've been waiting so long for this.
我们脑补过太多
And we've built it up in our heads so much.
各位  这只是部电影而已
Guys, it's just a movie.
没错
That's true.
-他说得对  -的确
- He's right. - It is.
不过  我们都记得扎扎
Although, we all remember Jar Jar.
莱纳德  我又开始提心吊胆了
Leonard, I-I'm scared again.
我比预想中更享受
Well, I enjoyed that more than I thought I would.
奴家也是
Me, too.
我很期待你下次过生日时
I look forward to your next birthday
我们再做一次
when we do it again.
这样奴家也愿意
That works for me.
我比预想中更享受这电影呢
I enjoyed that more than I thought I would.
我爽得都走不动了
I don't think I can walk right now.
谢尔顿
Uh, Sheldon?
Sheldon.
亚瑟
Arthur.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
我不需要什么建议了
I-I don't think I need any more advice.
我只是好奇嘛
I-I was just curious.
那事儿最后怎么样了
How-How'd it go?
非常棒
It was amazing.
几天之后我去看了
I-I saw it a few days later.
电影超赞
What a movie.
那...  艾米呢
But, uh, what-what about Amy?
她也挺喜欢的
Uh, uh, she liked it fine.
不过她不像我  对这个系列作有感情
But she doesn't have the history with the franchise I do.
好吧
Okay.
好吧  聊得挺开心
Good... good talk.